what's up everyone welcome back to the
second channel so as you guys know these
Samsung Galaxy S 10 light just got
announced yesterday and I didn't get a
chance to do the Galaxy S and E versus
the s10 light quick comparison that I
wanted to do but I figured I would drop
it on the second channel a quick
disclaimer the galaxy has time the light
is not available for everyone to own yet
it was just strictly announced I've seen
a couple of videos here and there people
owning one but or really Samsung giving
them the right to use some footage or
some like that but I wanted to do a
quick comparison to see what the main
differences are between both of these
phones now technically speaking these
will be some of the cheapest Samsung
Galaxy flagship II type of phones that
Samsung will put out now I was kind of
confused why Samsung would push the
galaxy s 10 light so far into the life
cycle of this 10 series when the S 20 or
s11 is about to come out but we kind of
saw Google do the same thing with the
pixel 3 a so it's really not that big of
a deal anymore I don't think after I put
a little bit of thought into it now
looking at the front of both these
phones the Samsung Galaxy S 10 has a
five point eight inch dynamic AMOLED
display that one is a 1080p display and
that one was a really good panel I'm not
gonna lie it was very good every which
way I looked at it I mean yeah it wasn't
a quad HD or anything it wasn't like a
crazy cool looking panel but because it
was smaller it didn't really look too
pixelated the PPI did the pixels per
inch density was actually pretty high
but the galaxy s 10 light has a six
point seven inch full HD Super AMOLED
display they both have infinity o
displays but the Samsung Galaxy S 10
lights is in the center but that's 10
light will be not only a bigger phone
than the galaxy s 10 II but also the
galaxy s 10 I mean that's pretty crazy
we don't really see light or budget
phones being bigger than the actual
phone itself then the flagship phone so
it's really weird that resolution on
that panel is 1080p by 2400 a little bit
higher resolution panel but it's because
it was just a bigger panel but the PPI
is smaller on the galaxy s 10 light so
there's technically less pixels on that
display then on the galaxy s 10 deeper
inch so in terms of the panel's they'll
both look almost the same in my opinion
but I like how that stand lights
hole-punch displays in the center or
either destiny's which is in the top
right corner now turning both phones
around what's interesting is the galaxy
s 10 e actually has one less camera
sensor than that has tena light so we
have a dual camera setup on the galaxy s
10 e we have a 12 megapixel wide-angle
lens and then
16-megapixel ultralight sensor you're
able to do for Kade up to 60 frames per
second and that camera is actually
pretty good
I like that camera whenever I would use
it whenever I would do anything with it
I liked it a lot it was a very good
camera the gallic says 10 light however
has a triple camera setup it has a 5
megapixel macro lens a 48 megapixel
wide-angle lens and then a 12 megapixel
ultra-wide sensors so so that's really
cool we do have an extra sensor on the
galaxy s 10 light but I still have a
feeling that the galaxy s 10 e might
have the better camera sensor overall
but once I actually go ahead and get the
s 10 light I'll go ahead do a full on
comparison between them but in terms of
the cameras and everything I'm sure
they'll be around the same type of
quality and features and all that but I
sell with feeling the S 10 D might be
the better camera sensor overall now
getting into the performance side of
things this is where things might get a
little interesting so the galaxy s 10 D
has a Qualcomm Snapdragon 855 chipset an
octa-core CPU with 6 gigabytes of RAM on
the base model and then eight gigabytes
of RAM on the top tier model and the
Galaxy S 10 light follows the same exact
thing you know it has the octa-core
processor we don't know yet whether it
has a Qualcomm Snapdragon 855 or in
other chips that we really don't know
yet but people are suggesting that it is
getting the 855 and the RAM is the same
exact way we either get six or eight
gigabytes of RAM whether you want the
base model or the top tier model however
one thing that we are noting is that
there's only a 128 gigabyte storage
model but there is probably a microSD
card slot on it so it shouldn't be that
crazy of a deal with solis that's a good
thing now ending it off with the battery
life in the battery size mostly so the
galaxy s 10 D had a 30 100 million power
battery and that battery life was kind
of it was pretty average I think it was
a little bit above average but it wasn't
anything crazy the s10 plus had a pretty
good battery life the s10 had pretty
decent battery life destiny was ok the
galaxy s 10 light however has a 4,500
million for her battery which is insane
at a phone of this caliber the cheaper
phone of the regular s10 has a bigger
sized battery than the standard models
which doesn't make much sense to me but
it does have a way bigger battery size
than the galaxy s 10 II so between
battery life the galaxy s tonight will
have the bigger advantage so to kind of
sum up this quick comparison should you
wait for the s10 life to be fully
announced or should you pick up a Galaxy
S 10 II well we don't know what the
price set is of the S 10 light people
are estimating that is going to cost
$4.99 or something like that
five ninety-nine even which will still
technically be cheaper than a brand new
Galaxy S ten II but you can pick up a
used as tiny for like four hundred even
less than four hundred in the used
market you can pick up a standard as ten
for less than four hundred so I'll
probably recommend you if you need it
right now you can pick up a Galaxy S 10
II in the use market for like four
hundred less than four hundred or you
can always wait for that student like to
come out or wait for more details to
come out for it it never hurts to wait
for a phone especially when you know
what's about to come out so that's kind
of what I would suggest at this time but
that is pretty much it guys if you have
any other questions or anything leave it
down in the comment section below hit
that like button down me so much but
definitely the subscribe button every
single subscriber that would get really
discounts through me so much you guys
get hit that also check out the other
links down in the description as well my
Twitter my Instagram my main channel all
those things are linked down below I'd
really appreciate if you guys could
check it out but more importantly
everything also love every single one of
you guys all fall catch you guys in the
next video peace out :
[Music]